Preliminary Inventory of the Lee Edwards Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound recordings (Box 1, 8-11, 152-153, 163, 213-221, 330)
  - Sound recording of Barry Goldwater in Aug 1966, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0004856
    Goldwater answers Lee Edwards questions about the current and near future political landscape.
  - Sound recording of Maureen Reagan from July 1967, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0004855
    Maureen Reagan Sills speaks about her father, concentrating on various vignettes that shed light on his character.
  - Town Meeting of the World sound recording, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005339
    This tape contains a sound recording of Ronald Reagan debating Robert Kennedy on 15 May 1967. It sounds like it was recorded in a room where a few people, including Lee Edwards, were listening to the event and commenting on it.
    There are also other recordings on the same tape.
  - Willard Edwards report to the Human Events Political Action Conference, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005356
    Edwards speaks about media bias against Richard Nixon in the 1960 presidential campaign.
  - Willard Edwards speech at Knox College on 14 Dec 1961, 2 sound open reel tapes There are 2 accessioned copies of this recording available. Copy 2 has an extent of 2 open reel tapes. (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005360
  - Willard Edwards speech at Knox College on 14 Dec 1961, 1.0 sound open reel tape; There are 2 accessioned copies of this recording available. Copy 2 has an extent of 2 open reel tapes. (Box 152)
  - Willard Edwards speech: JFK's Use of News as Weaponry, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 152)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005354
    This speech was given before the Human Events Fifth Political Action Conference and Homecoming for Conservatives at the Statler-Hilton Hotel in Washington, DC
  - 1983 APJC presidential campaign coverage conference sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006642
    Label reads: 1983 APJC- Presidential Campaign Coverage #5
  - 1986 Conservative Political Action Conference sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006653
    Lee Edwards hosts a panel discussion on how conservatives can deal with the media. The panelists are Mark Rhoades, Reba Ferris, and George Archibald.
  - An Audio View: Echoes of the American Republic sound recording from Jan 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006654
    Part 1:
    Introduction 1991 - Salute to Bush - William Hamilton - Peggy Noonan - Lew Rockwell - Midge Decter - Melor Sturua - Claudia Winkler
    Part 2:
    Pat Buchanan - Media Monitor - William Raspberry - Paul Farley - Phyllis Schlafly - Donald Zagoria - Antje Kraus
  - Center for Applied Economic Research conference sound recording, 7 Mar 1983, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006579
    Dr. Edwin Feulner speaks to a conference sponsored by the Center for Applied Economic Research. He is introduced by Antonio Martino and Lee Edwards.
  - Center for Applied Economic Research conference sound recording, 9 Mar 1983, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006580
    The speakers are Antonio Martino, H. Joachim Maître, Lee Edwards, and Dick Allen. Martino and Edwards function as masters of ceremonies. Maître speaks about criticisms by Germans about freedom and fascism. Allen is the main speaker.
  - Ecumedia News Audio Service interviews Lee Edwards in October 1990, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006647
    This interview concerns Walter Judd and Edwards' book on Judd.
  - Edwards family recital sound recordings from 1975, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006631
  - Edwards family sound recordings, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006992
    Catherine & Elizabeth 10/2/76
    Christmas Concert '78 (Elizabeth+Catherine)
    Elizabeth Edwards
    Goddard interview '76 (With Lee Edwards acting as Goddard)
    1. Rest in Land
    2. Divine Redeemer
  - Edwards-Sabatini recital sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006994
  - Howard Philips interviews Lee Edwards sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006655
    Howard Philips interviews Lee Edwards on the Washington Perspective program.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Boyd Crawford on 20 Jun 1985, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006636
    This interview concerns President Truman and the Republican congress.
    This interview is open. Other content on the original cassette is closed.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Dole in Jan 1987, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006581
  - Lee Edwards lecture from 18 Nov 1985, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006630
    Edwards speaks about the conservative movement. He analyzes the institutions and coalitions needs to sustain the movement. He also looks at the importance of Reagan in the current environment.
  - Little Flower Choir 1975 Christmas Mass sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006657
  - Little Flower Choir Christmas Eve 1984 music recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007010
  - Little Flower Choir Easter 1982 music recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007009
  - Little Flower Choir May 1978 recital sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006658
  - M. E. Lewis sound recording from 18 Oct 1985 and Lee Edwards interviewing Dr. Shaw, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006644
    Lewis speaks in a lecture/speech setting. She outlines how to do campaign/political mailings correctly. Also on the tape is an interview with M.E. Lewis.
    The original cassette tape also includes Lee Edwards interviewing a Dr. Shaw.
  - Missionary for Freedom: The Life and Times of Walter Judd audiobook, 13 sound cassettes (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006539
    Gerald Knight reads Lee Edwards' book "Missionary for Freedom: The Life and Times of Walter Judd" for the blind.
    Part 01: Chapters Begin and 1, page 1 - page 7
    Part 02: Chapter 01, page 007 to chapter 02, page 023
    Part 03: Chapter 02, page 023 to chapter 03, page 037
    Part 04: Chapter 03, page 037 to chapter 05, page 053
    Part 05: Chapter 05, page 053 to chapter 06, page 069
    Part 06: Chapter 06, page 069 to chapter 08, page 085
    Part 07: Chapter 08, page 085 to chapter 08, page 100
    Part 08: Chapter 08, page 100 to chapter 09, page 115
    Part 09: Chapter 09, page 115 to chapter 09, page 130
    Part 10: Chapter 09, page 130 to chapter 10, page 145
    Part 11: Chapter 10, page 145 to chapter 11, page 160
    Part 12: Chapter 11, page 160 to chapter 11, page 174
    Part 13: Chapter 11, page 174 to chapter 12, page 189
    Part 14: Chapter 12, page 189 to chapter 13, page 204
    Part 15: Chapter 13, page 204 to chapter 14, page 220
    Part 16: Chapter 14, page 220 to chapter 14, page 234
    Part 17: Chapter 14, page 234 to chapter 15, page 250
    Part 18: Chapter 15, page 250 to chapter 16, page 266
    Part 19: Chapter 16, page 266 to chapter 16, page 280
    Part 20: Chapter 16, page 280 to chapter 17, page 295
    Part 21: Chapter 17, page 295 to chapter 17, page 309
    Part 22: Chapter 17, page 309 to chapter 18, page 324
    Part 23: Chapter Postscript, page 325 to chapter Notes, page 336
    Part 24: Chapter Notes, page 336 to chapter Notes, page 347
    Part 25: Chapter Notes, page 347 to Biblio, page 355
  - Music recordings, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006656
    Pop/rock music idiom
  - National Tax Limitation Committee sound recording from 21 May 1981, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006991
    Speakers include Lee Edwards, Milton Friedman, U.S. Senators, and U.S. Representatives. The speakers, after giving a talk, take questions.
  - Profile radio program from Oct 1990, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006652
    This recording is the radio program Profile about Walter H. Judd. The guest is Lee Edwards, speaking about his biography of Judd.
  - Sabatini-Edwards recital sound recording from 17 May 1981, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006995
  - Sabatini-Edwards recital sound recording from Aug 1981, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006999
  - Unidentified interview concerning the Peace Corps and Lee Edwards radio interview on WNTR, sound recordings, 1 sound cassette (Box 153)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0006651
    An unidentified woman interviews the Peace Corps country director for Malawi about the Peace Corps.
    This radio interview concerns Walter H. Judd and Edwards' biography of him.
  - Edwards and Sabatini recital music recording, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 163)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005386
  - Lee Edwards and Gloria Sabatini recital music recording, 1.0 sound open reel tape (Box 163)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0005389
    Musical performance
  - Lee Edwards interviews Anne Brumsdale on 15 Dec 1992, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007344
    This interview concerns Senator Barry Goldwater.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Charles Lichenstein on 12 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007019
    This interview is about Barry Goldwater.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Chas Lichenstein on 26 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007313
  - Lee Edwards interviews Clif White on 6 Apr 1992, 3 sound cassettes (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007033
  - Lee Edwards interviews Darrell Coover on 24 Nov 1992, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007339
  - Lee Edwards interviews David Franke on 28 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007323
  - Lee Edwards interviews Doris Berry on 2 Jun 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007326
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Feulner on 20 Apr 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007352
    This interview concerns Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement. Feulner speaks relatively quietly, and, due to the low audio quality of the original microcassette, is not always intelligible.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Meese on 12 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007046
    This interview is about Barry Goldwater and how the former Senator figures into the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews James Buckley on 19 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007302
  - Lee Edwards interviews James Day on 13 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007053
  - Lee Edwards interviews James Hinish on 4 Jun 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007358
    Lee Edwards interviews James Hinish with a focus on Barry Goldwater. However, the conversation branches out to the conservative movement as a whole, contemporary politics, and Hinish's career in politics.
  - Lee Edwards interviews James Hobson on 27 Jul 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007368
    This interview is about Senator Barry Goldwater and the 1964 campaign.
  - Lee Edwards interviews James M. Perry on 27 Jul 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007336
  - Lee Edwards interviews James McFadden on 20 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007308
  - Lee Edwards interviews James Streeter on 30 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007034
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jeremiah Milbank on 20 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007307
  - Lee Edwards interviews John McGowan on 6 Jan 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007334
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Sears on 9 Jun 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007330
  - Lee Edwards interviews Judge Pamela Rymer on 2 Sep 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007335
  - Lee Edwards interviews Karl Hess on 22 Jun 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007333
    Interviewed as part of Edwards' research for his Goldwater biography, this interview covers a wide variety of topics. In addition to Goldwater, topics include, but are not limited to, motorcycles, nights in jail, Ayn Rand (and comparing her to Jack London), conservatism, libertarianism, Pat Buchanan, America First, the relationship between information and authority.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Mark Rhodes on 17 Jun 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007364
    Lee Edwards interviews Mark Rhodes about Barry Goldwater and politics in the 1960s. The conversation also includes a discussion about Rhodes' work with Phil Crane.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Philip Crane on 19 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007303
  - Lee Edwards interviews Richard Wirthlin on 10 Jun 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007331
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Croll on 2 Oct 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007374
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Merry on 17 Jun 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007332
  - Lee Edwards interviews Steve Hess on 16 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007057
  - Lee Edwards interviews Terry Emersen on 27 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007314
  - Lee Edwards interviews Terry Emerson on 27 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007032
  - Lee Edwards interviews Tom Reed on 7 Jan 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007347
    This interview concerns Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews William A. Rusher on 22 Feb 1992, 2 sound cassettes (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007020
  - Lee Edwards interviews William Timmons on 8 Jun 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007329
  - Mark Davis radio interview with Ty Ross, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007379
    The men discuss gay rights issues and how they relate to Ross and his maternal grandfather, Barry Goldwater.
  - Sound recordings of Barry Goldwater television appearances in 1993, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 213)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007078
    Barry Goldwater appears on CNN's Larry King Live on 10 Jun 1993 and the Tonight Show with Jay Leno on 12 Nov 1993.
    It sounds like Edwards recorded the program from a microphone that was in the room with him and his wife as he watched the programs on television.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Allan Ryskind on 28 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007704
    This interview concerns Senator Barry Goldwater, especially his relationship with the Hopi tribe.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Anna Chennault on 13 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007712
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bruce Weinrod on 12 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007698
  - Lee Edwards interviews Donald Devine on 7 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007694
  - Lee Edwards interviews Donald Lambro on 20 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007716
    This interview concerns Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement of the 20th century.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed McCabe on 23 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007718
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ernest Le Jever on 13 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007699
  - Lee Edwards interviews Howard Baker on 10 Nov 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007739
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ivan Sidney on 6 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007705
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Howard on 25 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007732
  - Lee Edwards interviews M. E. Lewis on 24 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007721
  - Lee Edwards interviews Michael Baroody on 14 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007723
  - Lee Edwards interviews Midge Decter on 31 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007722
  - Lee Edwards interviews Pat Hutar on 15 Aug 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007733
    Label reads:
    Pat Hutar 8/15/93
    (also John Grenier)
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Laxalt on 10 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007711
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Weyrich on 16 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007726
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Weyrich on 18 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007700
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ralph de Toledano on 18 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007713
  - Lee Edwards interviews Reed Larsen on 19 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007715
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Bauman on 11 Sep 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007734
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Creighton on 7 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007708
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Novak on 18 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007727
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Tyrrell on 20 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007728
  - Lee Edwards interviews Stan Evans on 20 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007717
  - Lee Edwards interviews Vic Gold on 10 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007695
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter Mears on 21 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007701
  - Lee Edwards interviews William Rickenbacker on 23 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007729
  - Lee Edwards interviews William Schulz on 10 Mar 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 214)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007709
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ben Wattenberg on 29 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008478
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bill Middendorf on 26 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008034
    This interview is about Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement in the United States.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bob Mardran on 19 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008017
  - Lee Edwards interviews Brent Bozell on 10 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008024
  - Lee Edwards interviews Carol Dawson on 31 Jan 1992, 2 sound cassettes (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008048
  - Lee Edwards interviews D. Kitchel on 16 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007999
    Also on the tape is the end of an unrelated event hosted by Lee Edwards from 9 Oct 1986.
  - Lee Edwards interviews David Keene on 3 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008470
    This interview is about Senator Barry Goldwater.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Earl and Judy Eisenhower on 19 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008014
    This interview is about Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement within the Republican Party.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Harry Rosenzwey on 18 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008009
  - Lee Edwards interviews Henry Salvatori on 9 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007988
  - Lee Edwards interviews Howard Phillips on 6 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008475
  - Lee Edwards interviews J. A. Parker on 30 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008044
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jack Germond on 29 Apr 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008477
    This interview is about Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jack Williams on 18 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008012
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Kolbe on 22 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008021
  - Lee Edwards interviews Leonard Liggio on 28 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008040
    This interview is about Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Lyn Nofziger on 23 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008037
  - Lee Edwards interviews Morton Blackwell on 13 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008026
  - Lee Edwards interviews Neal Freeman on 7 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008476
    This interview concerns Barry Goldwater, 1960s NY politics, and the 1964 presidential election.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Patricia Bozell on 12 May 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008481
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Fannin on 17 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008004
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Wagner on 21 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008032
    Edwards and Wagner discuss Senator Barry Goldwater and the conservative movement of the 20th century.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Prescott Budge Ruffner on 21 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008018
  - Lee Edwards interviews Richard Viguerie on 5 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008474
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Goldwater on 18 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)